Guide to the Isaac Levi Papers, 1949-2014 ASP.2016.04
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Correspondence, 1949-2014; I.
  - Probability and Decision Theory Correspondence, c. 1950s-2007; 3.
    - Olson, Mancur, 1977-1984 (Box 23, Folder 26-27)
    - Osherson, Daniel et al, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Pais, John and Peter Jackson, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Papers on Justification of Reason, c. 1980s (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Paradox of Liberalism, c. 1970s (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Parfit, Derek and Newcombe, 1980s (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Parikh, Rohit, 1991-1999 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Pattanaik, Prasanta, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Payne, John W., 1976-1986 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Pearce, David G, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Pearl, Judea (Probability and Nomonotonic Reasoning), 1990-1995 (Box 23, Folder 37-38)
    - Pearl, Judea, 1983-1995 (Box 23, Folder 39-40)
    - Pepitone, Albert and Henri Zukier, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - Persson, Johannes, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - Pollack, R.A. and Douglas H. Blair, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 43)
    - Pollack, R.A. and E.S. Phelps, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 44)
    - Pollack, R.A., undated (Box 23, Folder 45)
    - Poole, David, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 46)
    - Pope, Robin E., 1986-1992 (Box 23, Folder 47)
    - Pratt, John W. and Richard J. Zeckhauser, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 48)
    - Pressler, Jonathan, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Rabinowicz, Wlodek, 1994-1996 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Rabinowicz, Wlodek, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Ramsey, F.P., 1992 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Reny, Phillip and Susan Elmes, undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Roberts, Kevin W.S., 1980 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Rubin, Herman, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Rubinstein, Ariel, 1988-2003 (Box 24, Folder 8-10)
    - Sahlin, Nils-Eric, 1988-1990 (Box 24, Folder 11-13)
    - Samet, Dov, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Schick, Frederic, 1965-1966 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Schick, Frederic, 1968-1969 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Schick, Frederic, 1972-1985 (Box 24, Folder 17-18)
    - Schick, Frederic, 1980-1989 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Schick, Frederic, The Theory of Pure Democracy, undated (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Schmeidler, David, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Segal, Uzi, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Segerberg, Krister, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Sen, Amartya, 1977-1979 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Sen, Amartya, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Sen, Amartya, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Sen, Amartya, c. 1970s (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Sen, Amartya, Columbia University John Dewey Lectures, September 1984 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Sen, Amartya, On Economic Inequality, undated (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Sen, Amartya, 1992-2000 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Shier, Ju, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Shoham, Yoav, 1988-1993 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Simon, Herbert A., undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Slovic, Paul and Amos Tversky, c. 1960s-1970s (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Sobel, Matthew J., 1980-1996 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Stalknaker, Robert, c. 1990s (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Stirling, Wynn, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Strotz, Robert H., c. 1950s (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Suzumura, Kotaro and Yongsheng Xu, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Suzumura, Kotaro, 1988-1990 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Tennant, Neil, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Trapp, R.W., undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Tversky, Amos, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Urchs, Max, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Van der Meyden, Ron, undated (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Von Weizsacker, Carl C., c. 1970s (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Vossenkuhl, Wilhelm, undated (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Wakker, Peter P., 2000 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Walliser, Bernard, undated (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Williams, Mary-Anne, 1994-1998 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Winter, Sydney G., undated (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Yaari, Menahem, Bar-Hillel, Maya and Margalit, Avishai, 1992-1994 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Collaboration with Teddy Seidenfeld, 1974-2014; 4.
    Subseries 4. Collaboration with Teddy Seidenfeld contains scholarly and professional correspondence files kept by Levi regarding his collaboration with Teddy Seidenfeld, whom Levi served as Doctoral Advisor and was Herbert A. Simon Professor of Philosophy and Statistics at Cernegie Mellon University. Included are correspondence files documenting publication drafts, conference presentations as well as Seidenfeld's collaboration with scholars M.J. Schervish and J.B. Kadane regarding Bayesian theory and statistics.
    - Consensus, Rationality and Pareto Unanimity (Reply to Teddy on Consensus), 1988-1989 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - DeGroot, Morris H., 1974 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Goldstein, Michael, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Kadane, J.B., 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Kadane, J.B., 1986 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Kadane, J.B., 1988-1990 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Kadane, Joseph B. and Genest, Christian, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Kullback, S. and Leibler, R.A., undated (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Philosophy of Science Association (PSA) (Teddy Seidenfeld), 1996 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Schervish, Mark J., 1983-1986 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Seidenfeld, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 33-34)
    - Seidenfeld- Decision Theory Without Ordering, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Seidenfeld- When Normal and Extensive Form Decisions Differ, 1994-2010 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Seidenfeld, Schervish and Kadane- Coherent Choice Functions Under Uncertainty, undated (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Seidenfeld, Schervish and Kadane- Improper Regular Conditional Distributions, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - Seidenfeld, Schervish and Kadane- Is Ignorance Bliss?, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - Seidenfeld, Schervish and Kadane On the Shared Preferences of Two Bayesian Decision Makers, October 27, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Seidenfeld, Schervish and Kadane State Dependent Utilities/Partially Ordered Preferences, 1989-1990 (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Seidenfeld, Schervish and Kadane Two Measures of Incoherence, How Not to Gamble if You Must, July 1997 (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - Seidenfeld, Schervish and Kadane, May 2000 (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Seidenfeld, Schervish and Kadane, 2002-2014 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Seidenfeld, Schervish and Kadane, 2012 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Seidenfeld, Schervish and Kadane, 2014 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Seidenfeld, Schervish and Kadane, c. 2004 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Seidenfeld, Schervish and Kadane, Cooperative Decisions and Coherent Choice Functions, PSA, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Seidenfeld, Teddy, c. 1980s (Box 26, Folder 6-7)
    - Seidenfeld, Teddy, c. 1987-1991 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Seidenfeld, Teddy- American Statistical Association (ASA), 2002 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Seidenfeld, Teddy and Deborah G. Mayo, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Seidenfeld, Teddy and Geisser, Seymour on Arnold Zellner's Bayesian Method of Moments (BMOM), c. 1996 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Seidenfeld, Teddy and Mark J. Schervish, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Seidenfeld, Teddy and Schervish, Mark Draft Proposals, 1986-1987 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Seidenfeld, Teddy Calibration Prospect Theory, undated (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Seidenfeld, Teddy Correspondence and Papers, 1978-1981 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Seidenfeld, Teddy Correspondence and Papers, 1983-1987 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Seidenfeld, Teddy Correspondence and Papers, 2007-2008 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Seidenfeld, Teddy Correspondence and Papers, 2008-2012 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Seidenfeld, Teddy Correspondence and Papers, Spring 2011 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Seidenfeld, Teddy Correspondence and Papers, c. 1976 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Seidenfeld, Teddy Correspondence and Papers, c. 1999 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Seidenfeld, Teddy Correspondence and Papers, 2011 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Seidenfeld, Teddy- Decision Theory Without Ordering, 1985-1990 (Box 26, Folder 23-25)
    - Seidenfeld, Teddy on Nonconglomerability, etc., 1980 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Seidenfeld, Teddy Unbounded Utilities in Two Domains and Racing Photos, undated (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Seidenfeld, Teddy, When at Oxford, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Seidenfeld, Teddy, Fall 1984 (Box 27, Folder 2-3)
    - Seidenfeld, Teddy, Speeches, c. 1980s-1990s (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Seidenfeld, Teddy: Peas in a Pod: Some Recipes For Cooking Mendel's Data, 1997-1999 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Seidenfeld, Teddy: Review of Minnesota Studies, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Seidenfeld-Levi Correspondence, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Collaboration with Horatio Arlo-Acosta, 1990-2011; 5.
    Subseries 5. Collaboration with Horatio Arlo-Acosta contains scholarly and professional correspondence files kept by Levi regarding his collaboration with Horatio Arlo-Acosta, whom Levi served as Doctoral Advisor and professor of Philosophy at Carnegie Mellon University. Included are correspondence files documenting publication drafts and conference presentations.
    - Arlo-Costa, Horacio and Dov Samet, 1997-1998 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Arlo-Costa, Horacio and Jeff Helzner, Experience/Description, 2011 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Arlo-Costa, Horacio Belief Revision Conditionals: Basic Iterated Systems, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Arlo-Costa, Horacio Conditionals: from Philosophy to Computer Science, undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Arlo-Costa, Horacio Correspondence and Papers, 1994-1995 (Box 27, Folder 12-14)
    - Arlo-Costa, Horacio Correspondence and Papers, 1996-1998 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Arlo-Costa, Horacio Correspondence and Papers, 1997-1998 (Box 27, Folder 16-17)
    - Arlo-Costa, Horacio Correspondence and Papers, 1997-2001 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Arlo-Costa, Horacio Correspondence and Papers, 2000-2008 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Arlo-Costa, Horacio Correspondence and Papers, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 20-21)
    - Arlo-Costa, Horacio Correspondence and Papers, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Arlo-Costa, Horacio Correspondence and Papers, 2005 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Arlo-Costa, Horacio Correspondence and Papers, 2006-2007 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Arlo-Costa, Horacio Correspondence and Papers, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 1-4)
    - Arlo-Costa, Horacio Research Proposal and Budget, 1994-1995 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Arlo-Costa, Horacio Saturatable Contradiction, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Arlo-Costa, Horacio, Summer 2001 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Arlo-Costa, Horatio on Choice Functions, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Helzner, Jeffrey, undated (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Neighborhood Semantics, Arlo Costa et al, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Parikh, Rohit and Chopra, Samir, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Pedersen, Arthur Paul and Arlo-Costa, Horacio Social Norms, Rational Choice and Belief Change, undated (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Pedersen, Arthur Paul, undated (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Shapiro, Scott J. and Horacio Arlo-Costa, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Lectures and Speeches, 1968-2010; II.
  Series II. Lectures and Speeches contains drafts, notes, information and correspondence regarding various presentations Levi delivered worldwide throughout his academic career.
  - 5 Question Epistemology, undated (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - 5 Question Probability and Statistics, 2008 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - A Paradox for the Birds, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Acceptance Revisited, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Albert's Problem, undated (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Alchourro Memorial, undated (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - American Philosophical Society (APA) (Cleveland), 1969 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - APA Western Division Meeting (Braithwaite), 1968 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Association for Symbolic Logic, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Assorted Writings and Presentations, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Behavioral and Brain Sciences, 1978-1983 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Behavioral Research Council (BRC) Dewey Symposium, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Beware of Syllogism: Statistical Reasoning and Conjecturing According to Peirce, December 2001 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Castignioncello Workshop, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Certainty, Probability and the Correction of Evidence, March 28, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Chance Transparencies, undated (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Coherence, Regularity and Conditional Probabilities, 1977-1978 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Comment on Braithwaite (University of Western Ontario Philosophy Colloquium), 1969 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Comment on Ian Hacking "Inductive Logic" at Salzburg, 1968-1969 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Comment on Ian Hacking Responses for Salzburg, 1968-1969 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Conference on Applications of Inductive Logic, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Conference on Rationality and Naturalism, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Consensus and Doubt Presentation Transparencies, undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Consensus and Shared Agreement and Outcome Theory, 1983-1985 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Consistency Preserving Conditionals Transparencies, undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Contraction and Informal Value, undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Contraction and Informational Value, 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Correlated Equilibrium and Common Knowledge of Rationality Slides, undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Corrigibilism Without Solidarity, June 2001 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Dagstuhl Seminar, 2009 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Degrees of Belief and Dagstuhl Seminar, 2007 (Box 29, Folder 12-13)
  - Degrees of Belief Final Version, 2007-2008 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Degrees of Belief: Konstanz, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Degrees of Belief: Maximizing and Satisficing Degrees of Belief, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Degrees of Belief: Money Pumps and Diachronic Dutch Books (PSA), 2000 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Degrees of Belief: Transparencies for Shackles Measure (Konstanz), 2004 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Deliberation Crowds Out Prediction (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Demons of Decision, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Dewey, John: Postmodernism and Beyond (Simon's Rock College of Bard), 2001 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Dynamic Dutchbook Arguments are Incoherent! (PSA), 2000 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Ernst Nagel Festschrift, undated (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Evidential Support Presentation Transparencies, undated (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Festschrift for Wlodek Rabinowicz, 1995-1996 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - FEW (Berkley), 2007 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - For Ghent, Belgium Talk Presentation Transparencies, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Four Themes in Statistical Explanation (UC Irvine) (Box 29, Folder 28-29)
  - Four Types of Ignorance, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Frankfurt Transparencies, undated (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - G.L.S. Shackle, Festschrift, 1970-1971 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Game Theory (Vienna), 1996 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Genot, Emmanuel J. and Erik J. Olsson and Paris Workshop, December 2008 (Box 30, Folder 1-2)
  - Hard Choice (APA Pacific Division), 1989 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Hintfest (Jaakko Hintikka), 1994 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - History of Science Society (HAS) and Philosophy of Science Association (PSA) Vancouver, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 5-6)
  - Hollisfest (Martin Hollis), 2004 (Box 30, Folder 7-8)
  - Incognizables, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Induction According to Pierce Presentation Transparencies, undated (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Inductive Appraisal, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Inductive Expansion According to Caution Dependent, Deductively Cogent and Partition Sensitive Criteria, undated (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Inductive Expansion and Nonmonotonic Reasoning, undated (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Intermediate Probability and Change of View, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Interval Probability Workshop, Munich, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Jerusalem, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 16-17)
  - Keynes on the Weight of Argument, c. 2010 (Box 30, Folder 18-19)
  - Kyburg Conference, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Kyburg Presentations, 1991-1992 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Kyburg, Henry E. Comments on APA, undated (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Kyburg, Henry E. Memorial and Symposium, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Kyburg, Henry Memorial Symposium (University of Rochester), 2004 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Leipzig Workshop, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Levifest Replies (Columbia University), 2004 (Box 30, Folder 26-27)
  - London (Regensburg – Lund), May 2000 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Marburg European Consortium for Political Research (ECPR) Conference, 2003 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Marcus, Ruth, Festschrift, 1992-1994 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Meeting on Scientific Change, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Money Pumps and Diachronic Dutch Books (PSA), 2000-2002 (Box 31, Folder 4-6)
  - New School Talk on Ernest Nagel, undated (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - New School Talk, May 1978 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Nonmonotonic Reasoning Transparencies, undated (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - On the Good Ship Episteme (University of Western Ontario Philosophy Colloquium), 1969 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Overheads: Ellsberg, undated (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Oxford (Thyssen), 1978 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Oxford, 1977-1978 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Padua, Italy (Minimal Rationality), 2003 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Peirce and Popper Abduction With or Without Induction, November 2002 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Peterfest (Peter Gardenfors), 1999 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Philosophy of Science Association (PSA), 1983-1984 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Philosophy of Science Association (PSA), 1984 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Philosophy of Science of Association (PSA), 1978 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Pittsburgh Talk on Nonmonotonic Reasoning, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Pragmatism, Fallibilism and Corrigibility, April-May 2001 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Prediction, Bayesian Deliberation and Correlated Equilibrium (Vienna Circle), 1995-1996 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Presentation Transparencies (assorted), undated (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Presentation Transparencies, undated (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Probability and Evidence (Philadelphia), 1968-1969 (Box 32, Folder 1-2)
  - Probability Logic and Logical Probability Presentation Pages, undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Rabinowicz, Wlodek, Festchrift, 2006 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Ramsey Conference, 2003-2004 (Box 32, Folder 5-6)
  - Reason and Nature, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Review of James Joyce: The Foundations of Causal Decision Theory, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Rutgers University Seminar on Bayesian Inference and Econometrics, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Saarbucken Conference, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Salzburg University, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 11-12)
  - Second Worst in Practical Conflict, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Serious Possibility, 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Society for Imprecise Probability Theories and Applications (SIPTA), 2005 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Society for Imprecise Probability Theories and Applications (SIPTA), 2007 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Society for Imprecise Probability Theories and Applications (SIPTA), 2009 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Society for Imprecise Probability Theories and Applications (SIPTA), 1982 (Box 32, Folder 18-19)
  - Steinfest (Howard Stein), 1999-2002 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Suppes Festschrift, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Symposium on: Cognition and Rationality, I: Minimal Rationality, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Talk at Graduate Center on Logic of Full Belief, undated (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Talks on Evidential Support, undated (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Theoretical Aspects of Rationality and Knowledge (TARK) Conference, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 25-26)
  - Transparencies for Orlando, undated (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Trento, Italy (International Nonmonotonic Reasoning Workshop), 1998-1999 (Box 33, Folder 1-2)
  - University of Cincinnati Philosophy Colloquium, 1969-1970 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - University of Florida Seminar on Bayesian Inference and Econometrics, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Uppsala Presentation Transparencies, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Vossenkuhl Wilhelm (Trip to Munich), 1995 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Wartofsky Fest, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Why I Am Not a Probabalist, c. 2008 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Why Indeterminacy in Probability Judgement (Version 2), 2007 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Why Indeterminacy in Probability Judgement, Isaac Levi Transparencies, 2007 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Why Indeterminate Probability is Rational (for Dagstuhl), 2007 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Wittgenstein Lectures and Slides, 1990-1991 (Box 33, Folder 12-13)
- Research and Reviews, 1949-2014; III.
  Series III. Research and Reviews contains draft manuscripts, notes, correspondence, publications and scholarly reviews written by Levi throughout his academic career. Files are organized alphabetically by name or topic and reflect Levi's original labeling of materials.
  - "Chance" by Isaac Levi, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - "A Note on Newcombmania", 1981 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - "Acceptance Revisited", 1974-1977 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science Meeting (AAAS), 1967 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - "Are Statistical Hypotheses Covering Laws?", 1968 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - "Are Statistical Hypotheses Covering Laws?", 1969 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Army, undated (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Articles and Publishing Information, c. 1983 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Articles and Publishing Information, c. 1984 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Articles and Publishing Information, c. 2001 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Articles and Publishing Information, c. 2007 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - "Assessing Accident Risks in Nuclear Power Plants", 1981 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - "Base Rates", 1980 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - "Bayesianism With a Human Face and Imprecision and Indeterminacy in Probability Judgement", 1983-1986 (Box 33, Folder 27-29)
  - Behavioral and Brain Sciences Jonathan J. Koehler Article, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - "Belief and Action", 1964 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - "Belief and Disposition", 1964 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - "Belief Change", 1997 (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - "Belief, Doubt and Self Criticism", 2007 (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - Bibliography for Marshall Swain Induction, Acceptance and Rational Belief, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Brandom, Robert B. "Making It Explicit" Review, 1994-1995 (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - Burks, A.W., Review by Levi, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Cambridge Dictionary of Philosophy Ernst Nagel, 1990-1991 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Cambridge on Second Book, 1985-1986 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Canadian Journal of Philosophy, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Carnap, Rudolph, "The Old and the New Logic", undated (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - "Chance" (Philosophical Topics), Fall 1990 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - "Changing Probability Judgements", 1994 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Cohen L.J. and M. Hesse, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - "Commitment and Change of View", 2001 (Box 34, Folder 9-10)
  - "Common Causes: Smoking and Lung Cancer", 1983 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - "Compromising Bayesianism", 1987-1989 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - "Confirmation and Acceptance", 1965 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - "Confirmation and Acceptance", undated (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - "Confirmational Conditionalization", 1977-1978 (Box 34, Folder 15-16)
  - "Conflict and Inquiry" (Final Version), 1989-1992 (Box 34, Folder 17-18)
  - "Conflict and Social Agency", 1981 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - "Conflict and Social Agency", 1982 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - "Conjunctive Bliss", 1983 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - "Consensus and Doubt", 1997 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - "Consensus, Rationality, and Pareto Unanimity", 1992 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - "Consequentialism and Sequential Choice", 1989-1990 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - "Consonance, Dissonance and Evidentiary Mechanisms", 1983 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - "Contextualist Epistemology", 2005-2008 (Box 34, Folder 26-27)
  - "Contracting from Epistemic Hell is Routine", 2003 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - "Convexity and Separability in Representing Consensus", undated (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence and Reviews, 2007-2008 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence and Reviews, 2012 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence and Reviews, c. 1990s (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Book, 1977-1978 (Box 35, Folder 2)